Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Sasha Abramsky on Voting Rights; Jeffrey Shandler on Adventures in Yiddishland with Alisa Solomon; Leslie Cagan on Anti-war Demonstration, 2006-09-17; cuid35580 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_103)
- "Under Siege: American Democracy in the Age of Bush" with Katha Pollitt, Patricia Williams, Elizabeth Holtzman, and Laura Flanders, 2006-09-24; cuid35581 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_53)
- Freida Lee Mock on Wrestling with Angels; Excerpts from "Under Siege: American Democracy in the Age of Bush" Panel at Brooklyn College Book Festival with Laura Flanders, Patricia Williams, and Elizabeth Holzman, 2006-09-24; cuid35582 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_104)
- Dena Hammerstein on My Name is Rachel Corrie; David Zellnik on Ariel Sharon Stands at the Temple Mount and Dreams of Theodor Herzl; Abe Velez Interviews Jeffrey Lewis with Live Music, 2006-10-06; cuid35583 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_105)
- Abe Velez Interview with Jeffrey Lewis, 2006-10-07; cuid35584 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_93)
- Antony Beevor and Luba Vinogradova on A Writer at War, 2006-10-12; cuid35585 (Box 19, Item 718_0787)
- Hanon Reznikov reading from Vasily Grossman's A Writer at War, 2006-10-15; cuid35586 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_55)
- Antony Beevor, editor and translator of Vasily Grossman's A Writer at War, 2006-10-15; cuid35587 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_57)
- Marathon Special on Vasily Grossman with Judith Malina, Hanon Reznikov, Antony Beevor, and Robert Chandler, Disc 1, 2006-10-15; cuid35588 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_106)
- Marathon Special on Vasily Grossman with Judith Malina, Hanon Reznikov, Antony Beevor, and Robert Chandler, Disc 2, 2006-10-15; cuid35589 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_107)
- Scott Ritter and Seymour Hersh on Iran at Ethical Culture Institute (Special Sponsored by The Nation), 2006-10-16; cuid35590 (Box 19, Item 718_0784)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interview with Robin Becker, 2006-10-17; cuid35591 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_60)
- Mark Crispin Miller on 2004 Elections and His Book Fooled Again; 2006 Mid-Term Elections with Jennifer Siegel, 2006-10-29; cuid35592 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_68)
- Ruchama Marton of Israel Committee for Residency Rights, 2006-11-02; cuid35593 (Box 19, Item 718_0795)
- Scott Ritter on Iran's Nuclear Programs, US War Plans, and His Book Target Iran; Mona El-Farra on the Humanitarian Crisis in Gaza; Michael Ratner on the Military Commission Act, 2006-11-05; cuid35594 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_76)
- Robin Becker; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz; Aziz Abu Sarah; Parents Circle: Families Forum, 2006-11-12; cuid35595 (Box 19, Item 718_0796)
- Ann Snitow Remembers Ellen Willis; John Green on the Evangelical Vote; Wendy Weiser on 2006 Elections; Nahanni Rous on the Film Encounter Point, 2006-11-12; cuid35596 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_69)
- Adrienne Rich at Center for LGBTQ Studies (CLAGS) Annual Kessler Lecture, 2006-11-17; cuid35597 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_54)
- Muriel Rukeyser Special with Jan Heller Levi, Suzanne Gardinier, and Adrienne Rich, 2006-11-26; cuid35598 (Box 19, Item 718_0781)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-11-26; cuid35599 (Box 19, Item 718_0790)
- Suzanne Gardinier (Track 1); Adrienne Rich (Track 2); Hugh Seidman (Track 3); Jan Heller Levi (Track 4); Interview (Track 5), 2006-11-26; cuid35600 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_52)
- Rukeyser Tribute Panel: Jan Heller Levi Interview, 2006-11-26; cuid35601 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_56)
- Muriel Rukeyser Special with Jan Heller Levi, Suzanne Gardinier, and Adrienne Rich, 2006-11-26; cuid35602 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_70)
- Jim Hoberman on Borat; Vincent Panama Alba on Shooting of Sean Bell by NYPD, 2006-12-03; cuid35603 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_71)
- Alisa Solomon Interview with Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-12-24; cuid35604 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_59)
- Esther Kaplan and Abe Velez on FCC; Jed Abrahamian on Iran; Alisa Solomon Interviews Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-12-24; cuid35605 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_72)
- Brian Walt of Rabbis for Human Rights; Lisa Jervis and Andi Zeisler on the 10th Anniversary of Bitch Magazine; Joann Sfar on The Rabbi's Cat, 2006-12-31; cuid35606 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_98)
- Rashid Khalidi [2015-018], circa 2007-2011; cuid35607 (Box 20, Item 718_1013)
- Rabbi Marc Gellman [2015-021], circa 2007-2014; cuid35608 (Box 20, Item 718_1018)
- Geoffrey Aronson on Israeli Settlement Expansion; Sara Roy and Daniel Sievadsky on AJC Report on Anti-Semitic Jews, 2007-01-07; cuid35609 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_124)
- Rev. Osagyefo Sekou on 1/27 March and Martin Luther King, Jr.; Jim Hoberman and Richard Pena on Jewish Film Festival; Michael Ratner Remembers Bob Boehm; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Remembers Tillie Olsen, 2007-01-14; cuid35610 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_131)
- Rashid Khalidi for 2/4/2007 Marathon, 2007-02-04; cuid35611 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_112)
- Ali Abunimah on One Country: Introduction and Reading (Track 1), Interview (Track 2), 2007-02-04; cuid35612 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_115)
- Ruchama Marton, 2007-02-04; cuid35613 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_123)
- Marathon: Ali Abunimah on One Country: A Bold Proposal to End the Israeli-Palestinian Impasse; Rashid Khalidi on The Iron Cage: The Story of the Palestinian Struggle for Statehood; Dr. Ruchama Marton on the Israeli Committee for the Right of Residency; Dr. Tarik Ramahi on Efforts to Enter Israel, Disc 2, 2007-02-04; cuid35614 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_166)
- Marathon Special, 2007-02-04; cuid35615 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_169)
- Interview with Shulamit Aloni on Jimmy Carter's Book Palestine: Peace Not Apartheid, 2007-02-11; cuid35616 (Box 19, Item 718_0805)
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on the New Congress; Ed Case on Jewish Population Surveys; Rebecca Manski on Negev Development Plans, 2007-02-11; cuid35617 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_167)
- Shulamit Aloni and Steven Friedman on Apartheid and Israel, 2007-02-18; cuid35618 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_116)
- Neil Baldwin on Mitt Romney's Presidential Candidacy Announcement; Shulamit Aloni and Steven Freedman on Apartheid and Israel; James Shapiro on Theater for a New Audience Productions of The Merchant of Venice and The Jew of Malta, 2007-02-18; cuid35619 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_168)
- Phyllis Bennis on Iran: How Likely is War?; Steven Beeber on The Heebie-Jeebies at CBGBs: a Secret History of Jewish Punk, 2007-02-25; cuid35620 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_163)
- Peter Miller on The Internationale, 2007-03-03; cuid35621 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_121)
- Udi Aloni on Effort by Israeli Consulate in Paris to Prevent His Film Forgiveness from Opening at the Israeli Film Festival; Sarita Gupta and Sheldon Freedman on the Employee Free Choice Act; Michael Weinstein on With God on Our Side: One Man's War Against an Evangelical Coup in America's Military, 2007-03-04; cuid35622 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_155)
- Peter Miller on Sacco and Vanzetti, 2007-03-11; cuid35623 (Box 19, Item 718_0808)
- Sue Udry on Anti-war Proposals in Congress and 3/18 Demonstration in New York City; Julie Wiener on Her In the Mix Column; Iver Bernstein on New York Divided: Slavery and the Civil War Exhibition, 2007-03-11; cuid35624 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_170)
- Eric Sawyer on Act-Up's 20th Anniversary; Alexander Nowak and Atina Grossman on Germany's Re-naturalization Program; Andre Schiffrin on A Political Education: Coming of Age in Paris and New York, 2007-03-18; cuid35625 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_165)
- J.J. Goldberg, 2007-03-21; cuid35626 (Box 19, Item 718_0813)
- Tanya Reinhardt Remembrance; J.J. Goldberg on American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) Conference and Vice President Cheney; Nan Rubin Interviews Michael Dorf; Abe Valez Interviews Frank London, 2007-03-25; cuid35627 (Box 19, Item 718_0799)
- J.J. Goldberg on Cheney's AIPAC Speech, 2007-03-25; cuid35628 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_113)
- Remembering Tanya Reinhardt; J.J. Goldberg on Dick Cheney's Speech at the Annual AIPAC Assembly; Michael Dorfman on the Downtown Jewish Cultural Scene; Frank London on the Klezmatics' Emmy Award for their Woody Guthrie CD, 2007-03-25; cuid35629 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_184)
- Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti, 2007-04-01; cuid35630 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_120)
- Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism, 2007-04-01; cuid35631 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_164)
- Phyllis Bennis on Riyadh Summit; Rachel Kahn-Troster on Admission of LGBTQ to the Jewish Theological Seminary; Alicia Svigals on Her Series at The Stone, 2007-04-08; cuid35632 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_162)
- Chris Hedges on American Fascists: The Christian Right and the War on America; Annette Ezekiel, Leader of the Band Golem, 2007-04-15; cuid35633 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_161)
- Scott Sherman and Rashid Khalidi on The New York Sun at Five Years; Natasha Winegar and Anderson Fils-Aime on New York is Our Home Campaign; Laurel Reuter on Los Desaparecidos Exhibition, 2007-04-22; cuid35634 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_159)
- Sarah Henry and Moe Fishman on Fighting Fascism: New York and the Spanish Civil War; Yousef Jabareen on The Future Vision of the Palestinian Arabs in Israel; Yael Lehrer Interview, 2007-04-29; cuid35635 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_158)
- Peter Miller on The Internationale, Part 1, 2007-04-30; cuid35636 (Box 19, Item 718_0818)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-04-30; cuid35637 (Box 19, Item 718_0822)
- Gail Levin on Becoming Judy Chicago; Seymour Lachman on Three Men in a Room; Rachel Leon on Reforming New York State's Dysfunctional Government System, 2007-05-06; cuid35638 (Box 19, Item 718_0817)
- Gail Levin on Becoming Judy Chicago; Seymour Lachman on Three Men in a Room; Rachel Leon on Reforming New York State's Dysfunctional Government System, 2007-05-06; cuid35639 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_157)
- The Internationale with Peter Miller, Part 2, 2007-05-13; cuid35640 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_152)
- Marathon Special on The Internationale with Peter Miller (Partial), Part 1, 2007-05-13; cuid35641 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_156)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz interviews Rebecca Goldstein on Betraying Spinoza; Lore Segal on Shakespeare's Kitchen, 2007-05-22; cuid35642 (Box 19, Item 718_0812)
- Paul Buhle and Jenny Romaine on the 110th Anniversary of the Forward with Bintel Brief Readings; Abe Velez and Esther Kaplan Interview Ido Haar about 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27; cuid35643 (Box 19, Item 718_0820)
- Ido Haar on 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27; cuid35644 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_111)
- Abe Velez and Esther Kaplan Interview Ido Haar about His Film 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27; cuid35645 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_122)
- Paul Buhle and Jenny Romaine on the 110th Anniversary of the Forward; Ido Haar on His Film 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27; cuid35646 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_153)
- Josh Ruebner on "The World Says No to Israeli Occupation" Rally, 2007-06-03; cuid35647 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_117)
- Joyce Antler with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-06-03; cuid35648 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_126)
- Josh Ruebner on the US Campaign to End the Israel Occupation Rally 6/10-6/11; Alana Newhouse on A Living Lens: Photographs of Jewish Life from the Pages of the Forward; Joyce Antler on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-06-03; cuid35649 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_160)
- Tom Segev on 1967: Israel, the War, and the Year That Transformed the Middle East at Congregation B'nai Jeshurun (Partial), 2007-06-06; cuid35650 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_176)
- Abba Eban Addresses U.N. June 1967; Mouin Rabbani on Six Day War and Fallout; Tom Segev Talk at B'nai Jeshurun, 2007-06-10; cuid35651 (Box 19, Item 718_0801)
- 40th Anniversary of 1967 War: Abba Eban UN Address in June 1967, Mouin Rabbani Speaks from Jordan about 1967 and Its Consequences, Tom Segev from His Talk at Congregation B'nai Jeshurun, 2007-06-10; cuid35652 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_154)
- Aziz Abu Sarah of Parents Circle; Martin Duberman on His Book Cures; Arthur Goldberg of Jews Offering New Alternatives for Healing (JONAH), 2007-07-01; cuid35653 (Box 19, Item 718_0804)
- Aziz Abu Sarah on Palestinian Group of Parents Circle Families Forum (October 2006 Interview), 2007-07-01; cuid35654 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_100)
- Interview with Arthur Goldberg of JONAH, 2007-07-01; cuid35655 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_118)
- Aziz Abu Sarah of Palestinian Parents Circle-Families Forum; Martin Doberman on His Attempts at Reparative Therapy and His Book Cures; Arthur Goldberg of JONAH, 2007-07-01; cuid35656 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_148)
- Arthur Goldberg on JONAH and Jewish Reparative Therapy, 2007-07-01; cuid35657 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_179)
- Michel Warschawski on Jews and the Global War and the Division of Gaza and the West Bank; Roberto Rodriguez on Baila Gitano Baila and Danzon de Moises, 2007-07-08; cuid35658 (Box 19, Item 718_0806)
- Michel Warschawski on Jews, the Global War, the Division of Gaza and the West Bank; Roberto Rodriguez on Baila! Gitano Baila! and El Danzon de Moises, 2007-07-08; cuid35659 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_149)
- J.J. Goldberg, 2007-07-25; cuid35660 (Box 19, Item 718_0823)
- J.J. Goldberg World Jewish Congress Leadership Controversy; Michael Ratner on Court Decisions on Guantanamo and Habeas Corpus; Abe Velez on Viva la Guantanamera, 2007-07-29; cuid35661 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_150)
- J.J. Goldberg on World Jewish Congress and Jewish People's Planning Institute's Future of the Jewish People in Jerusalem Conference in July 2007, 2007-07-29; cuid35662 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_171)
- J.J. Goldberg on the Future of the Jewish People in Jerusalem Conference; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Bettina F. Aptheker on Memoir Intimate Politics; Mark Laiosa Interviews Kenneth Helphand on Defiant Gardens, 2007-08-05; cuid35663 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_151)
- Bettina Aptheker on Her Memoir Intimate Politics: How I Grew up Red, Fought for Free Speech, and Became a Feminist Rebel, 2007-08-05; cuid35664 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_174)
- Mabou Mines and Miller's Launch, 2007-08-06; cuid35665 (Box 19, Item 718_0824)
- Rebroadcast of 11/27/2005 Show: Karen Armstrong and Chip Berlet Speaking at Examining the Real Agenda of the Religious Far Right Conference, 2007-08-12; cuid35666 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_144)
- Peter Miller on Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism Biographies, 2007-08-19; cuid35667 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_109)
- Rebroadcast of 4/10/2007 Show: Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism, 2007-08-19; cuid35668 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_145)
- Stephen Walt and John Mearsheimer Book on the Israel Lobby; Rebroadcast of Phyllis Bennis with Joel Beinin (03/26/2007); Rebroadcast of Michael Massing Interview (06/11/2007), 2007-08-26; cuid35669 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_146)
- Israel Lobby with Phyllis Bennis, Joel Beinin, and Michael Massing (Rebroadcasts), 2007-08-26; cuid35670 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_181)
- Grace Paley and Moe Fishman Obituaries; Mike Wishnie on Immigrant ID Cards and ICE Raids in New Haven; Bhairavi Desai on Impending September 5 Strike Over GPS, 2007-09-02; cuid35671 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_147)
- Grace Paley Tribute with Vera Williams and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz; Eytan Fox on The Bubble, 2007-09-09; cuid35672 (Box 19, Item 718_0809)
- Grace Paley on Activism, Responsibility of a Poet, and on Writing with Vera Williams and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, 2007-09-09; cuid35673 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_125)
- Remembering Grace Paley with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Vera Williams; Eytan Fox on The Bubble Film, 2007-09-09; cuid35674 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_140)
- Eytan Fox on The Bubble, 2007-09-09; cuid35675 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_175)
- Debbie Howard and Mona El-Dahry on Khalil Gibran International Academy; Jennifer Siegel on Anti-Defamation League and Armenian Genocide, 2007-09-16; cuid35676 (Box 19, Item 718_0825)
- Deborah Howard and Mona Eldahry on Khalil Gibran International Academy; Jennifer Siegel on American Defamation League and Armenian Genocide, 2007-09-16; cuid35677 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_141)
- Roya Hakakian on US Jews and Iran; Rabbi Michael Lerner on AIPAC and Responses to Cong. Jim Moran Tikkun Interview; Dr. Zia Mian on Nuclear Policy, 2007-09-23; cuid35678 (Box 19, Item 718_0803)
- Roya Hakakian on U.S. Jews and Iran Policy; Michael Lerner on Rep. Jim Moran's Comments on AIPAC; Dr. Zia Mian on Nuclear Proliferation in Iran, Israel, India, and Pakistan, 2007-09-23; cuid35679 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_142)
- Jennifer Wallace, CD 1, 2007-09-30; cuid35680 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_119)
- Interviews with Dr. Jennifer Wallace, Alyson Cole, and Lore Segel, 2007-09-30; cuid35681 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_143)
- Lore Siegal on Shakespeare's Kitchen: Stories, 2007-09-30; cuid35682 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_172)
- Alyson Cole on Cult of True Victimhood: From the War on Welfare to the War on Terror, 2007-09-30; cuid35683 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_182)
- Peter Rachleff on University of St. Thomas and Desmond Tutu; Juliano Mer Khamis of the Jenin Freedom Theatre; Idan Raichel on New CD The Idan Raichel Project, 2007-10-07; cuid35684 (Box 19, Item 718_0802)
- Peter Rachleff on Uninviting Desmond Tutu to University of St. Thomas; Juliano Mer-Khamis of the Jenin Freedom Theater; Idan Raichel on the Idan Raichel Project, 2007-10-07; cuid35685 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_136)
- Naomi Klein on The Shock Doctrine; Jeremy Scahill on Blackwater, 2007-10-14; cuid35686 (Box 19, Item 718_0810)
- Marathon Special with Naomi Klein, Two Tracks, Disc 1, 2007-10-14; cuid35687 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_114)
- Marathon Special: Naomi Klein on The Shock Doctrine, Part 1, 2007-10-14; cuid35688 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_137)
- Marathon Special: Jeremy Scahill on Blackwater, Part 2, 2007-10-14; cuid35689 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_138)
- Jeremy Scahill on Blackwater: The Rise of the World's Most Powerful Mercenary Army, 2007-10-14; cuid35690 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_183)
- Barbara Olshansky on Michael Mukasey; Roger van Zwanenberg on Joel Kovel Controversy; Phyllis Bennis on Dismissal of "Los Angeles Eight" Case, 2007-11-04; cuid35691 (Box 19, Item 718_0815)
- Barbara Olshansky on Michael Mukasey Attorney General Nomination; Roger van Zwanenberg on Controversy Surrounding Distribution by University of Michigan Press of Joe Kovel's Overcoming Zionism; Phyllis Bennis on Dismissal of LA 8 Case After 20 Years, 2007-11-04; cuid35692 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_139)
- Akiva Eldar, 2007-11-09; cuid35693 (Box 19, Item 718_0800)
- Akiva Eldar on Lords of the Land, 2007-11-09; cuid35694 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_110)
- Larry Cohler-Esses and Laila al-Qabbani on Islamofascism Awareness Week; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on The Colors of Jews, 2007-11-11; cuid35695 (Box 19, Item 718_0821)
- Larry Cohler-Esses and Laila al-Qahtani on "Islamofascism Awareness Week" and the New McCarthyism; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on The Colors of Jews, 2007-11-11; cuid35696 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_132)
- Nan Rubin with Murray Zimiles on Gilded Lions and Jeweled Horses Exhibition, 2007-11-14; cuid35697 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_108)
- Charlie Cray on "Carried Interest" Tax; Saidiya Hartman on Lose Your Mother; Murray Zimbalist on Jewish Wood Carver Exhibit, 2007-11-18; cuid35698 (Box 19, Item 718_0798)
- Charlie Cray on Carried Interest Tax Reform; Saidiya Hartman on Lose Your Mother; Murray Zimiles on Gilded Lions & Jeweled Horses Exhibition, 2007-11-18; cuid35699 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_133)
- Saidiya Hartman on Lost Your Mother: A Journey Along the Atlantic Slave Route, 2007-11-18; cuid35700 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_177)
- Saidiya Hartman, 2007-11-18; cuid35701 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_178)
- Akiva Eldar and Naomi Klein, 2007-11-25; cuid35702 (Box 19, Item 718_0811)
- Akiva Eldar on Israeli Settler Movement; Naomi Klein on Shock Doctrine, 2007-11-25; cuid35703 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_134)
- Mikado (Michel Warschawski), 2007-11-30; cuid35704 (Box 19, Item 718_0819)
- Michel Warschawski on Annapolis Talks; Danny Fingeroth on Jews and Comics; D.J. Handler and Smadar Levi on the Sephardic Jewish Music Festival, 2007-12-02; cuid35705 (Box 19, Item 718_0816)
- Michel Warschawski on Annapolis Talks; Nan Rubin with Danny Fingeroth on Jews and Comics; D.J. Handler and Smadar Levi on the Sephardic Jewish Music Festival, 2007-12-02; cuid35706 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_135)
- Michel Warschawski on the Annapolis Conference, 2007-12-02; cuid35707 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_173)
- Michael German on the Violent Radicalization and Homegrown Terrorism Prevention Act; Diane Crispo and Stefan Shaefer on Arranged; Alisa Solomon on Hanukkah, 2007-12-09; cuid35708 (Box 19, Item 718_0814)
- Michael German on the Violent Radicalization and Homegrown Terrorism Prevention Act; Stefan Schaefer and Diane Crespo on Arranged; Co-host Alisa Solomon on Hanukkah, 2007-12-09; cuid35709 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_128)
- Avner Cohen on Israel and the Bomb; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Ruth Behar on An Island Called Home, 2007-12-23; cuid35710 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_129)
- Avner Cohen on Nuclear Policy between US and Israel by Nixon and Meier, 2007-12-23; cuid35711 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_180)
- Remembering: Bob Boehm, Tillie Olsen, Tanya Reinhart, Moe Fishman, and Grace Paley, 2007-12-30; cuid35712 (Box 19, Item 718_0807)
- Obituaries: Bob Boehm, Tillie Olsen, Tanya Reinhart, Moe Fishman, and Grace Paley, 2007-12-30; cuid35713 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_127)